export default {

  difficulty1: [
    {
      question: 'In a tennis tournament, the player who loses goes home.\nIf 128 games were played throughout the tournament,\nhow many players were there at the start of the tournament?',
      response1: '64',
      response2: '128',
      response3: '127',
      response4: '129',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '20',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'How much is a quarter of a third?',
      response1: '1/12',
      response2: '3/4',
      response3: '1/7',
      response4: '4/3',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'I have 20 meters of red ribbon to make gift bows.\nFor each bow I need 50 centimeters of ribbon.\nHow many ties can I make?',
      response1: '30 gift bows',
      response2: '70 gift bows',
      response3: '40 gift bows',
      response4: '100 gift bows',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '20',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'I have to travel by bus for 1.5 hours and then wait 45 minutes for a train.\nThe train will drop me off at my destination two and a half hours later.\nHow long is my trip?',
      response1: '4 and a half hours',
      response2: '4 hours y 45 minutes',
      response3: '260 minutes',
      response4: '5 and quarter hours',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '25',
      difficulty: '1',
    },

    {
      question: 'A map is to scale where two centimeters is one kilometer.\nHow much would a route that is actually 20 kilometers long represent on the map?\nIn the real world, how long will a 9-centimeter road be on the map?',
      response1: '40 y 4 kilometers respectively',
      response2: '40 kilometers y 45 centimeters',
      response3: '40 y 45 centimeters respectively',
      response4: '40 centimeters y 4,5 kilometers',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '30',
      difficulty: '1',
    },
  ],

  difficulty2: [
    {
      question: 'I buy a pencil and a pen and pay $1 in total.\nIf the pen costs 30 cents more than the pencil, how much does the pen cost?',
      response1: '30 cents',
      response2: '70 cents',
      response3: '35 cents',
      response4: '65 cents',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '30',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'How much will a product have to be lowered so that the price is the same\nas it was before its price increased by 25%?',
      response1: '20%',
      response2: '25%',
      response3: '75%',
      response4: '50%',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '30',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: '3 (x-4) = 18. Which is the value of x?',
      response1: '6',
      response2: '14/3',
      response3: '22/3',
      response4: '10',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '20',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'If X is less than Y by a difference of 6 and Y is twice Z,\nwhat is the value of X when Z equals 2?',
      response1: '-4',
      response2: '2',
      response3: '-2',
      response4: '4',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '20',
      difficulty: '2',
    },

    {
      question: 'Alberto, Benjamin and Carlota made a total of 20 sandwiches.\nBenjamin did 3 times as much as Alberto, and Carlota did twice as much as Benjamin.\nHow many sandwiches did Alberto make?',
      response1: '2',
      response2: '4',
      response3: '5',
      response4: '6',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '30',
      difficulty: '2',
    },
  ],

  difficulty3: [
    {
      question: 'Each student can choose between 4 types of t-shirt and three types of pants.\nHow many possible combinations of uniform are there?',
      response1: '10',
      response2: '24',
      response3: '12',
      response4: '7',
      correctAnswer: '3',
      time: '20',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'A chef is going to prepare a vegetable salad with tomato, carrot, potato and onion.\nHow many ways can the salad be made using only 2 ingredients?',
      response1: '4',
      response2: '6',
      response3: '7',
      response4: '8',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '30',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'Eduardo, Carlos and Sergio have participated in a painting competition.\nThe competition awards is $200 to first place and $100 to second.\nHow many ways can the first and second place prizes be distributed?',
      response1: '4',
      response2: '6',
      response3: '7',
      response4: '8',
      correctAnswer: '2',
      time: '25',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'What is the first derivative of f(x) = ln(x)',
      response1: '2ln(x)',
      response2: '1',
      response3: 'x/2',
      response4: '1/x',
      correctAnswer: '4',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },

    {
      question: 'What is the integral of cos(x)?',
      response1: 'sen(x) + c',
      response2: 'cos(x)sen(x) + c',
      response3: 'tan(x) + c',
      response4: 'arccos(x) + c',
      correctAnswer: '1',
      time: '15',
      difficulty: '3',
    },
  ],
};
